oldnavy.ca 2008-12-17

# Privacy Policy | Old Navy Canada

## Our Commitment to Privacy

Gap Inc. and our affiliates in the U.S. and Canada, including Gap (Canada) Inc. and Old Navy (Canada) Inc. (collectively, "Gap Companies"), and our brands, including Gap, Banana Republic, Old Navy, Gap Factory Store, and Banana Republic Factory Store (collectively, our “brands”), value our customers and respect your privacy. We collect information about you in our stores and through our websites in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, contests and promotions. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. As described in this policy, we may share your information among our brands and, under certain circumstances, with third parties that provide services on our behalf or with whom we have partnered to offer a particular product or service.

This policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it, and when we share it with third parties. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. If our information practices change, we will post an updated policy on our website. You can tell if the policy has changed by checking the revision date that appears at the end of this policy. If we change the policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate notice to you. You may exercise your choices about how we collect and use your information consistent with this policy at any time.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below.

## Privacy Policy

  * »What kind of personal information do Gap Companies collect?
  * »How do Gap Companies use personal information?
  * »Do Gap Companies share personal information about me?
  * »How do I access or change personal information?
  * »How do I make choices about personal information?
  * »How do Gap Companies protect kids' privacy?
  * »How do Gap Companies use cookies?
  * »How do Gap Companies use pixel tags?
  * »How do I know personal information about me is secure?
  * »What is "phishing"?
  * »What about links to other websites?
  * »How do I contact you?

### What kind of personal information do Gap Companies collect?

We may collect personal information from you, such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, credit card number, gender, birthday, personal interests, etc., when you visit one of our websites or stores, place an order online or by phone, make an in-store purchase, save your information with us online, return an item to a store, contact us with a question or concern, or participate in a contest, promotion, or survey. We maintain a record of your product interests and the purchases you make online or by phone and in our stores. We may combine all of this information with information about you that we acquire from our joint marketing partners, from unrelated third parties, and from our other brands.

Information about you will be stored in servers hosted in the U.S. and Canada.

back to top

### How do Gap Companies use personal information?

We may use your personal information in the following ways:

  * »To process and fulfill your order, including to send you emails to confirm your order status and shipment 
  * »To communicate with you and to send you information by email, postal mail, telephone, text message, or other means about our products, services, contests, and promotions, unless you have directed us not to contact you with promotional communications 
  * »To administer and fulfill our contests and other promotions 
  * »To help us learn more about your shopping preferences
  * »To learn more about your shopping interests and purchasing history so that we can tailor offers and promotions to you 
  * »To help us address problems with and improve our site design, products and services 
  * »To enhance your shopping experience
  * »To process merchandise returns
  * »To analyze trends and statistics 
  * »To protect the security or integrity of our websites and our business 
  * »To contact you if necessary 

If you have questions or concerns about how we use personal information, please contact as indicated below in “How do I contact you?”

back to top

### Do Gap Companies share personal information about me?

We may share your personal information in the following ways:

  * »When you provide personal information to one of our Gap Companies, we may share that information with our other Gap Companies, which may be located in the United States or Canada.
  * »We may share information about you with our service providers who manage our customer information and perform services on our behalf, such as fulfilling promotions, sending communications to our customers, conducting surveys, etc. 
  * »We may share information about you when we team up with another company to offer or provide products, services, contests, or promotions to our customers. 

We require that all of these companies provide a comparable level of protection for personal information, including, in the case of our service providers, that they limit their use of personal information to providing these services to us.

In addition, if you choose to participate in any scrip, loyalty, or similar program in which a Gap Companies brand is a participating vendor, and you authorize Gap Companies or our credit card processor to provide information about purchases you make to the company administering the program, we will share personal information about you with that program. Scrip programs allow you to instruct us to divert a percentage of the amount you spend on purchases at our brands to participating schools and other non-profit organizations. Loyalty programs allow you to earn "points" on purchases at our brands, which you may then use toward certain rewards offered by the loyalty programs in which you participate. The information you authorize us to disclose to the scrip or loyalty program may include your credit card number and the date and amount of your purchase, and may also include your name and other information you have asked us to provide. Please note that once we disclose this information, the scrip or loyalty company may use and share it with others in accordance with its own privacy policy. You should review these policies carefully, as we have no control over them.

In the unlikely event of a sale or merger of Gap Companies or any of our businesses, personal information about our customers and other information we have collected as described in this policy may be among the transferred business assets and may be shared with other parties. Gap Companies also may disclose personal information about you in order to: (1) protect the legal rights, privacy or safety of Gap Companies or our employees, agents and contractors; (2) protect the safety and security of visitors to our websites or other properties; (3) protect against fraud or other illegal activity or for risk management purposes; (4) respond to inquiries or requests from government or public authorities in any country in which we operate, including the U.S.; (5) permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain; (6) enforce our Terms of Service; or (7) comply with the law or legal process.

back to top

### How do I access or change personal information?

You can ask us to change or update personal information about you by contacting us as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below. Please note that any request to update personal information may take up to 10 days for your email request and 6-8 weeks for your postal mail request.

back to top

### How do I make choices about personal information?

Gap Companies and our brands want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive promotional information, such as information about special offers and sales events, from one or more of our brands, you can let us know by contacting our customer service as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below.

Please be sure to include your full name and the email address you used when you registered with or made a purchase from the Gap Companies brand. If you ask us to remove your name and address from promotional lists, we will maintain your name in a "do not contact" file to ensure that we can honor your request. It may take up to 10 days to process your email request and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request, during which period you may continue to receive communications from Gap Companies.

If you change your mind, you can start receiving promotional communications from us again by signing up when you visit our websites or our stores or when you enter a sweepstakes or contest, or by contacting customer service.

If you have questions or concerns about how we use personal information about you or if you would prefer that we delete or suppress information we have about you, please us let us know by contacting our customer service as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below.

back to top

### How do Gap Companies protect kids' privacy?

Gap Companies is concerned about the privacy and safety of children when they use the Internet. We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information online from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. Our websites are general audience sites and are not targeted to or intended for use by children.

back to top

### How do Gap Companies use cookies?

Our websites use "cookies," which are small data files that are stored on your computer when you visit a website. Cookies may be used in a variety of ways to enhance or personalize your online experience.

For example, we may use cookies to enable you to use certain website features, store your preferences, recognize you when you return to our website, and monitor and maintain information about your use of our websites. Cookies may also be used to collect transaction information needed by a scrip or loyalty program to which you have authorized us to provide your personal information. (See the section entitled, "Do Gap Companies share my information?", above.)

You can set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide whether or not to accept it. If you do not accept cookies, however, certain features of our websites may not be available to you.

back to top

### How do Gap Companies use pixel tags?

We use "pixel tags" (also called "web beacons" or "clear gifs"), which are tiny graphic images, on our websites and in our emails. Pixel tags help us analyze our customers' online behavior and measure the effectiveness of our websites and our advertising. We work with service providers that help us track, collect, and analyze this information.

Pixel tags on our sites may be used to collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the features you use, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with the sites. This information may include your computer's Internet protocol (IP) address, your browser type, your operating system, date and time information, and other technical information about your computer. We may also track certain information about the identity of the website you visited immediately before coming to our site. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other websites. 

Pixel tags and cookies in our emails may be used to track your interactions with those messages, such as when you receive, open, or click a link in an email message from us.

We also work with third-party companies that use tracking technologies to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet. These companies may collect information about your visits to our websites and your interaction with our advertising and other communications. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having your information used by these companies, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. We may combine the information we collect through cookies and pixel tags with other information we have collected from you. This information may be used to improve our websites, to personalize your online experience, to tailor our communications with you, to determine the effectiveness of our advertising, to understand your preferences and for other internal business purposes.

back to top

### How do I know personal information about me is secure?

We do our best to provide you with a safe and convenient online experience. We have in place certain physical, electronic, contractual, and managerial safeguards to protect the security and privacy of your personal information.

When you enter your personal information on our websites, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your information as it is transmitted to us. To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit personal information, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. To double-check for security, look at the URL or Location line of your browser. If you have accessed a secure server, the first characters of the address in that line should change from "http" to "https."

back to top

### What is "phishing"?

"Phishing" is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an email that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other personal information through email.

back to top

### What about links to other websites?

For your convenience and information, our websites may contain links to other sites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked site. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any site that you access through our sites.

back to top

### How do I contact you?

For questions about our privacy policy, to make choices about receiving promotional communications, to update or change personal information about you in our databases, or to place an order, you can contact any of our Gap Companies brands by email, telephone, or postal mail:

back to top

Last Revised: August, 2008
